http://www.penntoolco.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Why does Penn Tool Co need my personal information?
Penn Tool Co uses your personal information to improve the overall shopping experience and provide you with better customer service. Knowing our customers allow us to contact our customers and ensure all their needs are met and any questions or concerns are handled appropriately and accurately. All personal information we acquire is provided by each individual customer. This information, allows our customer service team to provide knowledgeable support. Benefits you may receive by allowing us to keep your personal information on hand include:
A Personal Internet Account - You will be identified by Penn Tool Co every time you log in with your personal customer number so in the future you will save time by not having to submit your information again.Traceable Product Delivery - You will be able to track the location of your shipment through our online tracking system.Order Status Updates - You will receive order status updates through email notification, including order-confirmation and order-shipped.Updates on Internet Specials - You will receive updates on Internet specials you have requested, and invitations to join our Sweepstakes and giveaways.Personalized, Knowledgeable Customer Service - Our customer service team will be able to assist you promptly and accurately by identifying you and your preferences.Opting OutYou may withdraw your personal information at any time. To withdraw your information, email or write us at:
Penn Tool Co.1776 Springfield AvenueMaplewood, NJ 07040
Will Penn Tool Co sell my email address?
No. We will not sell, trade, share or rent your email address to anyone. Your email address is personal and should be kept that way. We use your email address to provide you with better customer service support, and to update you on our Internet specials as you requested.
×
OK
Get Special Offers & Savings
Surplus / Clearance
Customer Service
My Account
Order Status
Catalog Request
Stay Connected
Penn Tool Co.
1776 Springfield Avenue
Maplewood, NJ 07040
Ph: 800-526-4956
Fax: 973-761-1494
info@pentoolsco.com
Sitemap Privacy Terms & Conditions Returns Policy
Copyright 2020 Penn Tool Co., Inc. All Rights Reserved.
×
Guaranteed Lowest Prices
Satisfaction Guaranteed - If for any reason our products do not meet your expectations, return them. Complete refund or credit will be issued for unused and unmarked items returned within 10 days of receipt. Defective items will be either replaced or repaired.
Price Protection - Penn Tool Co will NOT BE UNDERSOLD. You will not see our advertised products at a lower price or we will refund or credit the difference. All claims must be made within 30 days of purchase. Proof of claim is required.
At Penn Tool Co we work hard to make sure that each time you purchase a tool, you are completely satisfied.To us, complete customer satisfaction means:
*Today’s most Technologically Advanced Tools necessary to meet demanding production and quality control requirements.*Competitively priced. Penn Tool Co prides itself on keeping our price low without sacrificing quality.*Prompt courteous service. Our customer service representatives are fully trained. Product knowledge and commitment to customer service guarantees that your order is processed the same day you place it.Even with customer service and price protection at the top of our complete customer satisfaction list, we know you want more. Our extensive inventory is yet another way to keep you satisfied. Our large selection of inventory lets us fill your order immediately and at a completion rate that is extremely high in our industry.
Look through our website. If you don’t see a tool that you require contact us and Penn Tool Co will be glad to find it for you with our signature low price guarantee.
